vampirefreaks.com 2015-11-20

# VampireFreaks.com - Privacy Policy

###  Vampirefreaks Privacy Policy

Vampirefreaks.com is a community website where users create their own profiles. The information we collect that is required for each profiles is email address and age. We collect email addresses to prevent users from creating multiple profiles. We collect age information in order to keep in compliance with internet laws and practices. Users under the age of 13 are not allowed to create profiles on this site. IP addresses are also logged in order to prevent multiple account creation. Users can upload personal information to their profiles, which becomes published online. We do not sell any user info or give away any of the information we collect unless we are asked by law enforcement officials to release information. While we do have administrators who monitor the site in order to keep things in order, we do not take responsibility for anything that users publish on the site. This service is provided as-is, and we do not make any claims as to the quality of service.   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).   
Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a data provider who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content.   These cookies contain no personally identifiable information.  The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address in an unreadable and encrypted form, and share with a data provider. Any identifiable information used for these cookies is solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these data provider cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>   
We will never give out your email address or any other personally identifiable information unless required to do so by law. 

Emails you will receive consist of site notifications for new messages and responses on your profile.   
There is an 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of every email we send you.   
You can also turn off email notifications by going to edit settings or removing your email. 

VampireFreaks  
9710 3rd Ave  
Brooklyn, NY
